Professional Staff Congress (CUNY) Faculty Arbitration Records 5594
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Professional Staff Congress (CUNY) Faculty Arbitration Records
1972-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
City University of New York (CUNY)
CUNY Professional Staff Congress
5594
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Faculty arbitration records and awards.
5667724
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 08, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 20, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Teachers' unions -- New York (State); College teachers -- New York (State); Collective labor agreements -- College teachers -- New York (State); City University of New York; Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York
5667724
- Awards., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Awards., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Awards., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clarion, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  v.2:no.1-4,6,7,8 (1972)
- Clarion, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  v.3:no.1-5,7 (1973)
- Clarion, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  v.4:no.1-9 (1974)
- Clarion, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  v.5:no.1,2,5-7,10 (1975)
- Clarion, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  v.6:no.2,3,5-9 (1976)
- Clarion, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  v.7:no.2,3 (1977)
- LC Reporter, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  v8:no.9 (1972:Mar. 27). Legislative Conference of the City University of New York.